{
    "subject": "Ray_Barnett",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Neela_Rasgotra",
    "human_readable": "Ray Barnett is married to Neela Rasgotra.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9173620343208313,
            "question": "To whom is Neela Rasgotra married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9078924059867859,
            "question": "Is Neela Rasgotra married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8791981339454651,
            "question": "Who is Ray Barnett married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8329337239265442,
            "question": "What is the nature of the relationship between Ray Barnett and Neela Rasgotra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6844953298568726,
            "question": "What is the name of Ray Barnett's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.573191225528717,
            "question": "Who is Ray Barnett's partner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19446790218353271,
            "question": "Name the two people who are married to each other."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.153695210814476,
            "question": "Is there a marriage described in this statement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10384912043809891,
            "question": "Who are the individuals involved in a marital relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06205863133072853,
            "question": "Can you identify a couple mentioned in this statement?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ray Barnett is married to Neela Rasgotra.",
            "html": "yago_8979_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the individuals involved in a marital relationship?",
            "html": "yago_8979_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a marriage described in this statement?",
            "html": "yago_8979_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the two people who are married to each other.",
            "html": "yago_8979_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8979_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8979_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8979_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8979_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8979_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8979_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8979_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8979_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8979_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8979_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nThe provided text describes Ray Barnett and Neela Rasgotra as having romantic interest in each other, but it does not state they are married.  Furthermore, the document mentions that Neela was initially married to Gallant before his death."
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not provide any information supporting that Ray Barnett is married to Neela Rasgotra. In fact, the documents indicate that Ray Barnett was married to Linda Barnett for almost 57 years and mentions a relationship with Neela but does not state they were married."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Ray Barnett passed away in 2024 and Neela Rasgotra is introduced in season 11 of ER, which was produced between 1994-2009. Therefore, they could not have been married after his death.",
            "category": 0
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Information provided details Ray's wife Linda Westerman Barnett, their marriage length, children and family. Additionally, the text describes Neela's relationship history including a marriage to Gallant prior to his death in Iraq.  There's no mention of a romantic or marital relationship between Ray and Neela.",
            "category": 0
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Ray Barnett is married to Linda Westerman Barnett throughout the given context. There is no mention of his marriage to Neela Rasgotra.",
            "category": 0
        }
    }
}